isubmit.com 2007-06-26

# 

By registering your information with us, you confirm that you have read, understood and agree to the provisions of this Privacy Policy and to our Terms of Service. Dialup Inc. is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe is an independent, non-profit organization whose mission is to build users' trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. Because Dialup Inc. wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe. This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for iSubmit.COM (http://www.isubmit.com), owned Dialup Inc. 

**Table of Contents**   
**1.What is iSubmit, and why is my information needed?   
2\. What information does Dialup Inc. gather/track and how is it used?   
3\. With whom does Dialup Inc. share the information?   
4\. How can I review, correct and update my personal information?   
5\. What types of communications does iSubmit send out?   
6\. How can I opt out of Dialup Inc's collection, use and distribution of my information?   
7\. How does Dialup Inc. protect my information from loss, misuse or alteration?   
8\. Whom can I ask if I have additional questions?   
9\. Miscellaneous Information   
**

The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this Web site, and does not cover information that may be collected through software downloaded from the site. If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact an iSubmit Support Representative by email (support@isubmit.com). If you do not receive acknowledgment of your inquiry, or if your inquiry is not satisfactorily addressed, you should then contact TRUSTe through the TRUSTe Watchdog Dispute Resolution Process (http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php). TRUSTe will serve as a liaison with the Web site to resolve your concerns. 

**1.What is iSubmit, and why is my information needed?**

iSubmit is a website submission service. We ensure our clients get thier websites listed as fast as possible and long lasting as possible. For this service, iSubmit charges a recurring monthly fee via credit card. Once a client registers with iSubmit, he/she can log into their account via internet connection through our home page, http://www.isubmit.com. In order for Dialup Inc to properly bill our customers, confirm they are U.S. based websites, and allow clients to log in to thier accounts, me must collect certain Personally Identifiable (Pieces) of Information (PII). 

Back to top

**2.What information does Dialup Inc. gather/track and how is it used?**

In order to use this Web site, you must first complete the registration form and create a user name and password. During registration you are required to provide two different types of information: Personal and Website. We use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you. 

PERSONAL INFORMATION: Username, Password, First Name, Last Name, Address, City, State, Zip, Phone, Email Address, Credit Card Type, Credit Card Number, Credit Card Expiration and Credit Card Identification Number. This information is used to ensure that our customers are from the United States. If the customer chooses to receive a "hard copy invoice", we will use this information to send you a monthly paper invoice. Also, this information is used to help identify a user who cannot remember his/her username and password. The billing information is used to confirm that you are the owner of the credit card, that the credit card is registered to a US customer, and that you have the credit card in your possession. We run all credit cards with the 3 or 4 digit card verification code, but do not record it in any databases. All credit card information you provide us, besides the card verification code, is recorded in our database and used for future transactions. 

WEBSITE INFORMATION: Website Headline, Website Description, Website URL, Website Keywords and Website Category. This information is used by ISUBMIT.COM to submit your website to search engines and directories on your behalf. 

PROFILE: We store information that we collect through cookies and log files to create a "profile" of your preferences. We do not tie your personally identifiable information, and your purchasing history, to information in the profile, in order to provide tailored promotions and marketing offers and to improve the content of the site for you. 

DEMOGRAPHIC / OTHER INFOMATION: As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, referring/exit pages, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users. Movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We do link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information. There are two exceptions to this: (1) IP addresses are tied to personally identifiable information to log you into your account and to have an IP Address / Timestamp data pair when you process your credit card in order to reduce fraud, (2) Your referring URL is tied to personally identifiable information in order for us to track advertising effectiveness. 

COOKIES: A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We do link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. We use session cookies to identify who you are in order to keep you logged into your account. A session ID cookie expires when you close you browser. When you first come to http://www.isubmit.com (main site), we will set one cookie which will identify which website you were at right before you came to our website. We use this information to determine which of our paid advertising customers are clicking thru to our website with. Once you sign up with iSubmit, you will need to log into your account. When you log into your account, we use three cookies to identify who you are: (1) IP Address, (2) Special Alpha-Numeric Code, (3) Date-Time Stamp. This information is used only to keep you logged into your account. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site. No third parties use cookies on our site. 

Dial Up Inc. (10683 Senda Acuario, San Diego, Ca 92130) is the sole owner of the information collected on ISUBMIT.COM. ISUBMIT.COM collects personally identifiable information from our users at several different points on our Web site. We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site. 

Back to top

**3.With whom does Dialup Inc. share the information?**

PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION: We do not share your Personally Identifiable Information (PII) (see Section 1 \- Personal Information above) with other third parties. Dialup Inc processes all credit card transactions internally and therefore does not share this information with third parties. 

WEBSITE INFORMATION: When you sign up with iSubmit, we will share ALL your website information (see Section 1 \- Website Information above) to over 350 third party search engines and directories in order for them to consider placing your website in their system. A list of all these third party search engines and directoriescan be found at <http://www.isubmit.com/?engines=home>. We do not provide any personally identifiable information to them. 

LIVE INTERNET CHAT SUPPORT: iSubmit uses a third party software called 'PHPLive!' (http://www.phplivesupport.com) from OSI Codes Inc. The representative you are talking to on the other end is an employee of Dialup Inc, but all information is recorded on PHPLive'ss servers. This information is only used by Dialup Inc management to assure proper quality control. PHPLive does not use the information submitted in the live chat for any other purpose than to provide the Live Chat service. 

Back to top

**4.How can I review, correct and update my personal information?**

If your personally identifiable information changes, you may update it by logging into your account and clicking on 'Update Account Information', or by contacting the site directly. See section 8 for contact information. 

Back to top

**5.What types of communications does iSubmit send out?**

You will receive three different types of these emails: 

EMAIL - 'WELCOME': You will receive one welcome email explaining what you need to do to get started. 

EMAIL - 'MONTHLY FEE': We will send you monthly emails reminding you that your credit card has been charged and that your submission for that month has went through. 

EMAIL - 'DECLINED CREDIT CARD / ACCOUNT CLOSED': If your credit card is declined, we will send you a one time email informing you of this and that your account has been closed. You will not receive any further emails from us after this point (if you do not reinstate your account). 

HARD COPY INVOICE: You have the option of receiving a hard copy invoice sent to you via postal mail. If you opt-in to this, you will receive an invoice once a month, after your credit card is charged. You will not receive any further postal mail from us. 

YOU WILL NOT RECEIVE: Dialup Inc will not send you any Special Offers/Updates or Newsletters. 

FUTURE CHANGES: Although we have no plans or desires at this time to share your information with any third parties, if this changes in the future, you will be notified when your personal information is collected by any third party that is not our agent/service provider, so you can make an informed choice as to whether or not to share your information with that party. 

Back to top

**6.How can I opt out of Dialup Inc's collection, use and distribution of my information?**

OPTING-OUT OF EMAILS: You MAY NOT opt out of receiving any of the three emails listed above. When you sign up at iSubmit, you must agree to receive these three emails. Since you will not be receiving any other types of emails from us, there is no email opt out solutions. 

OPTING-OUT OF POSTAL MAIL: We provide you the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having a hard copy invoice sent to you via postal mail. The first time you log into your account, you will be asked whether or not you wish to receive a hard copy invoice. If youchange your mind at a future time, you must contact a support representative at support@isubmit.com to change your hard copy opt-out setting. 

Back to top

**7.How does Dialup Inc. protect my information from loss, misuse or alteration?**

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number) on our registration or order form, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can send email us at support@isubmit.com. 

Back to top

**8.Whom can I ask if I have additional questions?**

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at: 

POSTAL: Dialup, Inc.  
PO Box 910325  
San Diego, Ca 92191. 

INTERNET: Email us at support@isubmit.com, or you can contact us during normal business hours by going to http://www.isubmit.com and clicking on 'Click here for live support..'. 

Back to top

**9.Miscellaneous Information**

CANCELLATION OF OUR SERVICE: If you no longer desire our service, you information is kept in our system for a period of 10 years. This is done to ensure that if you become a customer of ours again, you are not entitled to the free 30 day trial again. 

LINKS TO OTHER SITES: This Web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by ISUBMIT.COM. Please be aware that we, ISUBMIT.COM, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. 

CHANGES IN THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT: We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

BUSINESS TRANSACTIONS: In the event ISUBMIT.COM goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via email and prominent notice on our Web site for 30 days of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information. 

We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. 

Back to top
